https://penrhospark.com/privacy-cookies/

18 Hole Course
Online Booking (18 Hole)
The Red Kite 9 Hole Course
Online Booking (9 Hole)
privacy & cookies
Privacy Policy This privacy policy explains how “Penrhos Park, “Parc Penrhos”, “Penrhos Golf Club”, “Company”, St Teilo Ltd (‘we’) use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website. Topics:What information do we collect about you?• How will we use the information about you?• Access to your information and correction• Data Retention• Data Storage• Cookies• Other websites• Changes to our privacy policy• How to contact usWhat information do we collect about you?We collect information about you when you complete a form or ask us a question through our website. The forms we do this through and the data collected is listed below:-Contact FormGolf MembershipRed Kite MembershipLeisure MembershipName, address, contact number, email address, date of birthThis website uses cookies to improve visitor experience and analyse visitor behaviour.How will we use the information about you?We collect information about you in order to respond to your contact made through our form. Your data is then retained in accordance with the data retention policy section below.We will not share your information with any other organisation.Access to your information and correctionYou have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us using the details in the Contact Us section below.We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.Data RetentionWe will keep your data until you request we remove it. You can do this by emailing or writing to the addresses in the How to Contact Us section below.Data storageYour data is kept securely in data centres located within the United Kingdom.CookiesCookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information can be used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. This website uses cookies to improve visitor experience and analyse visitor behaviour. This policy will be updated if this should change. For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser.Other websitesOur website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.Changes to our privacy policyWe keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 21st May 2018.How to contact usPlease contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:• by email: info@penrhosgolf.co.uk• or write to us at:St Teilo LtdPenrhos ParkLlanrhystudCeredigionSY23 5AY
address
Penrhos Park
Llanrhystud
Aberystwyth
Ceredigion
SY23 5AY
Wales
Contact
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
